mailtrap.io 2016-04-26

# Privacy — Mailtrap

**Notice** — Notice is what this privacy policy that you're reading is all about. You are reading it, right? It's important! When we collect your personal information, we'll tell you how we're using it, any types of third parties to which we might disclose it, (other than "agents," such as vendors or contractors, who are only processing such information for us or at our direction), and the choices we offer you to limit the use of your information.

Notice will be provided in clear and conspicuous language when you are first asked to provide us with personal information, or as soon as practicable thereafter, and we'll notify you before we use the information for something other than the purpose for which it was originally collected. If anything in this policy seems unclear, please don't hesitate to contact us at [support@mailtrap.io](mailto:support@mailtrap.io), so we can address your question and possibly clarify this document.

Although most changes are likely to be minor, we may occasionally need to change this policy. If we do update it, we'll notify you either by posting the new policy on our Services, their blogs, or by emailing you the changes or a link to the modified document. (See the "Choice" section below for information about how we'll notify you if we change our policy regarding sensitive information.) In any case, the way we use information you provide will be covered by the privacy policy that was in effect at the time it was collected.

**Here are some of the ways we may use personal information you provide us:**

  * To allow you to register for our Services and to administer and process the registration
  * To communicate with you about our products, services and related issues
  * To evaluate the quality of our products and services, and to enhance your experience on our web sites
  * To maintain and administer our web sites and comply with our legal or internal obligations and policies
  * To transfer information to others as described in this policy or to satisfy our legal, regulatory, compliance, or auditing requirements
  * To charge you any fees and provide you with a receipt or resolve billing issues associated with your account

**Choice** — Choice is all about making sure you have the ability to control how we share your personal information with others. We never share any of your personal information with non-agent third parties.

We won't share your personal information with non-agent third parties unless we are required to do so by law, or if we believe in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect our property, rights or those of third parties or the public at large. It is possible that we may, on occasion, buy or sell assets from or to other companies. If that should occur, user information is typically one of the assets that get transferred. Similarly, if Railsware or most of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that we go out of business or enter bankruptcy, user information could be transferred or acquired. You should be aware that such events can occur, and that if it does, the buyer may continue to use your personal and non-personal information, but only as set forth in this policy. Other than in these rare circumstances, Railsware will not rent or sell potentially personally identifying information to anyone.

We may from time to time request some of your financial information for the purposes of completing transactions you have initiated through the Services, enrolling you in discount, rebate, and other programs in which you elect to participate, protecting against or identify possible fraudulent transactions, and otherwise as needed to manage our business.

It's hard to imagine that we would ever consider collecting, let alone sharing, sensitive information with a non-agent third party, but if such a day should come, we will first give you the opportunity to explicitly consent (opt-in) to such disclosure or to any use of the information for a purpose other than the one for which it was originally collected or previously authorized.

If you are a registered user of our Services and have supplied your email address, we may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what's going on with the Services. We generally use our Services to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of communication to a minimum. If we do send you information that you did not expressly request, we will provide you with a way to request that you don't get any similar notices (opt-out, unsubscribe, etc.).

**Onward Transfer** — Prior to providing agents with any personal information, we will obtain assurances that they will safeguard it in accordance with this policy. Examples of assurances that may be provided include:

  * A commitment that they will handle the information in accordance with this policy, or will provide the same level of protection, as required by the Safe Harbor Principles, subject to EU Directive 95/46/EC ("the EU Data Protection Directive");
  * Safe Harbor certification by the agent, or being subject to another European Commission adequacy finding.

In the unlikely event that we should discover that an agent is using personal information in a way that conflicts with this policy, we will take all reasonable steps to stop it immediately.

**Security** — All records containing personal or financial information are considered to be our property and are afforded confidential treatment at all times. We work hard to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of personal or financial information. All such electronic information is stored on restricted database servers, and is generally kept until such time as you may ask us to edit or delete it, as described below. We only disclose such information to our employees, contractors or affiliates that a) need to know that information in order to process it for us or to provide other services, and b) have agreed not to disclose it to others.

All interactions with our Services use the Transport Layer Security/Secure Sockets Layer (TLS/SSL) protocol. We use a third-party, industry-accepted Payment Gateway to securely process credit card transactions.

**Data Integrity** — In addition to assuring you that we will protect your personal information, we also want to make sure that it is reliable, accurate, and up-to-date. In order to do that, we provide:

**Access** — Upon request, we will provide you with reasonable access to the personal information we collect about you. Because personal information—for example, your email address—is required to use The Services, we retain personal information as long as your account is active. You will have the opportunity to correct, update, modify or delete this information updating your information in The Services. Additionally, there may be limits to the amount of information we can practically provide. For example, we may limit an individual's access to personal information where the burden or expense of providing access would be disproportionate to the risks to the individual's privacy or where doing so would violate others' rights.

**Enforcement** — We will conduct internal audits of our compliance with this privacy policy, including an annual self-assessment. Our employees take your privacy as seriously as we do, and we will take all reasonable measures against any employee found to be in violation of this policy.

If you have any concerns or complaints about how you think we've handled your personal information, please contact [support@mailtrap.io](mailto:support@mailtrap.io). We will work hard to investigate and resolve any complaints you might have.
